{
  "trivia": [
    {
      "question": "What is the shortest LOONA song, excluding intros?",
      "answer": ["one & only", "one and only"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which ODD EYE CIRCLE song has an English version?",
      "answer": ["loonatic"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "How many songs are on YeoJin's solo album?",
      "answer": ["3", "three"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the oldest member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["vivi"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the youngest member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["yeojin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What does \"yyxy\" stand for?",
      "answer": ["youth youth by young"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the \"slash\" in \"1/3\"?",
      "answer": ["yeojin"],
      "reward": { "min": 8, "max": 18 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of 1/3?",
      "answer": ["haseul"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of ODD EYE CIRCLE?",
      "answer": ["kim lip", "kimlip"],
      "reward": { "min": 7, "max": 17 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the leader of yyxy?",
      "answer": ["yves"],
      "reward": { "min": 7, "max": 17 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Out of \"Love Battery\", \"Fire\", \"Cherry Bomb\", and \"Full Moon\", which of these LOONA covers has a studio version?",
      "answer": ["love battery"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which member has a scar under their eye?",
      "answer": ["jinsoul"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which 1/3 song was remixed on Orbit 1.0?",
      "answer": ["love&live", "love & live", "love and live"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the English translation of the title of the \"Love & Live\" remix from Orbit 1.0?",
      "answer": ["i like it more now", "i like you more now"],
      "reward": { "min": 20, "max": 30 }
    },
    {
      "question": "How many members are in LOONA?",
      "answer": ["12", "twelve"],
      "reward": { "min": 1, "max": 1 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Olivia Hye's representative fruit?",
      "answer": ["blood plum", "bloodplum"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which member trained for the least amount of time?",
      "answer": ["olivia hye", "hyejoo"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which member trained for the longest amount of time?",
      "answer": ["hyunjin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "True or False: yyxy members and Choerry are the only members with representative fruits.",
      "answer": ["true"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was the music video for Let Me In filmed?",
      "answer": ["iceland"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Chuu's OST?",
      "answer": ["spring flower"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of JinSoul's OST?",
      "answer": ["as time goes"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the survival show HeeJin and HyunJin appeared on predebut?",
      "answer": ["mixnine", "mix nine", "mix9", "mix 9"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which member has been an MC on Fact iN Star?",
      "answer": ["yves"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which music video does **not** have a 4K version?",
      "answer": ["vivid"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the song that HeeJin's LG CF is set to?",
      "answer": ["lullaby"],
      "reward": { "min": 20, "max": 30 }
    },
    {
      "question": "How many songs include the phrase \"Hey boy\"?",
      "answer": ["3", "three"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What are you supposed to burn, according to So What?",
      "answer": ["yourself"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the hidden track on [#]?",
      "answer": ["day & night", "day and night", "day&night"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Approximately how large is the LOONA lightstick (in centimetres)?",
      "answer": ["43", "43cm", "43 cm"],
      "reward": { "min": 15, "max": 25 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What location is HeeJin associated with in 1/3?",
      "answer": ["france", "paris", "paris, france"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What location is HyunJin associated with in 1/3?",
      "answer": ["tokyo", "japan", "tokyo, japan"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What location is HaSeul associated with in 1/3?",
      "answer": ["iceland"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What location is ViVi associated with in 1/3",
      "answer": ["hong kong"],
      "reward": { "min": 10, "max": 20 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which member is afraid of pigeons?",
      "answer": ["heejin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What song was covered by Kim Lip & Chuu?",
      "answer": ["i see the light"],
      "reward": { "min": 15, "max": 25 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What song was covered by LOONA for their Halloween 2019 stage?",
      "answer": ["full moon"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Name a member who is part of the \"halloween subunit\".",
      "answer": [
        "yves",
        "kim lip",
        "kimlip",
        "heejin",
        "choerry",
        "yerim",
        "olivia hye",
        "hyejoo"
      ],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is HaSeul's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["bird", "white bird", "dove"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is HaSeul's representative color?",
      "answer": ["green"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is HaSeul's english name?",
      "answer": ["jane"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which member is scared of water?",
      "answer": ["haseul"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is ViVi's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["deer"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is ViVi's representative color?",
      "answer": ["pastel rose", "light pink"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Yves' representative color?",
      "answer": ["burgundy"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Yves' representative animal?",
      "answer": ["swan"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Yves' representative fruit?",
      "answer": ["apple"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is JinSoul's representative color?",
      "answer": ["blue"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is JinSoul's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["blue betta", "siamese fighter"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Kim Lip's representative color?",
      "answer": ["red"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Kim Lip's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["owl"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chuu's representative color?",
      "answer": ["peach"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chuu's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["penguin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chuu's representative fruit?",
      "answer": ["strawberry"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is HeeJin's representative color?",
      "answer": ["pink", "bright pink"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is HeeJin's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["rabbit", "bunny"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is HeeJin's English name?",
      "answer": ["zoe"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which member is allergic to fur?",
      "answer": ["heejin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is HyunJin's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["cat"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is HyunJin's representative color?",
      "answer": ["yellow"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Go Won's representative color?",
      "answer": ["eden green", "mint green", "mint"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Go Won's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["butterfly"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Go Won's representative fruit?",
      "answer": ["pineapple"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Go Won's dog?",
      "answer": ["bbomi"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Choerry's representative color?",
      "answer": ["purple"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Choerry's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["fruit bat"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "True or False: Choerry does not like cherries.",
      "answer": ["true"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "True or False: Choerry prefers being called by her real name.",
      "answer": ["true"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which member enjoys collecting pens?",
      "answer": ["choerry", "yerim"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Choerry's favorite color?",
      "answer": ["pink"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Olivia Hye's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["wolf"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Olivia Hye's representative color?",
      "answer": ["silver", "gray", "black", "white"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which member is nicknamed \"Boss Baby\"?",
      "answer": ["olivia hye", "hyejoo"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "True or False: Olivia Hye prefers being called by her real name.",
      "answer": ["true"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "True or False: Olivia Hye dislikes bubble tea.",
      "answer": ["true"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is YeoJin's representative color?",
      "answer": ["orange"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is YeoJin's representative animal?",
      "answer": ["frog"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is YeoJin's English name?",
      "answer": ["runa"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the shortest member?",
      "answer": ["yeojin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the tallest member?",
      "answer": ["yves"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 15 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of HeeJin's solo song?",
      "answer": ["vivid"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from HeeJin's album?",
      "answer": [
        "vivid acoustic mix",
        "vivid (acoustic mix)",
        "vivid acoustic ver",
        "vivid (acoustic ver)",
        "vivid acoustic"
      ],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of HyunJin's solo song?",
      "answer": ["around you"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from HyunJin's album?",
      "answer": ["i'll be there", "ill be there"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of HaSeul's solo song?",
      "answer": ["let me in"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from HaSeul's album?",
      "answer": ["the carol"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of YeoJin's solo song?",
      "answer": ["kiss later", "키스는 다음에"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What song from YeoJin's album does not include YeoJin?",
      "answer": ["my sunday"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of HeeJin and HyunJin's duet on YeoJin's album?",
      "answer": ["my sunday"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of HaSeul and YeoJin's duet?",
      "answer": ["my melody"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Vivi's duet with HaSeul?",
      "answer": ["everyday i love you", "edily"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from Vivi's album?",
      "answer": ["everyday i need you", "ediny"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which member featured on \"Everyday I Need You\"?",
      "answer": ["jinsoul"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Kim Lip's solo?",
      "answer": ["eclipse"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from Kim Lip's album?",
      "answer": ["twilight"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Western producer who worked on Twilight?",
      "answer": ["cha cha malone"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of JinSoul's solo?",
      "answer": ["singing in the rain"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from JinSoul's album?",
      "answer": ["love letter"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Choerry's solo?",
      "answer": ["love cherry motion"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from Choerry's album?",
      "answer": ["puzzle"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Yves' solo?",
      "answer": ["new"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from Yves' album?",
      "answer": ["d-1"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Chuu's solo?",
      "answer": ["heart attack"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from Chuu's album?",
      "answer": ["girl's talk", "girls talk"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Go Won's solo?",
      "answer": ["one and only", "one & only", "one&only"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from Go Won's album?",
      "answer": ["see saw"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "True or False: Olivia Hye featured on See Saw.",
      "answer": ["false"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Olivia Hye's solo?",
      "answer": ["egoist"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the B-side track from Olivia Hye's album?",
      "answer": ["rosy"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "True or False: JinSoul featured on Rosy.",
      "answer": ["false"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the hidden track only on copies of [X X] Limited A?",
      "answer": ["stay with me babe"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the hidden track only on copies of [X X] Limited B?",
      "answer": ["daydream"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "True or False: 365 was meant to be on La Maison LOONA.",
      "answer": ["false"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Go Won's favorite color?",
      "answer": ["lavender"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the first member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["heejin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the second member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["hyunjin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the third member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["haseul"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the fourth member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["yeojin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the fifth member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["vivi"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the sixth member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["kim lip", "kimlip"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the seventh member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["jinsoul"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the eighth member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["choerry", "yerim"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the ninth member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["yves"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the tenth member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["chuu"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the eleventh member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["go won", "gowon"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the twelfth member of LOONA?",
      "answer": ["olivia hye", "hyejoo"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "True or False: There is a rendezvous 18.6 music video.",
      "answer": ["true"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Go Won is the godmother of whose baby?",
      "answer": ["grimes", "elon musk", "grimes and elon musk"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the October girl?",
      "answer": ["heejin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Name one of the November girls.",
      "answer": ["hyunjin", "yves"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first November girl?",
      "answer": ["hyunjin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Name one of the December girls.",
      "answer": ["haseul", "chuu"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first December girl?",
      "answer": ["haseul"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Name one of the January girls.",
      "answer": ["yeojin", "go won", "gowon"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first January girl?",
      "answer": ["yeojin"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the April girl?",
      "answer": ["vivi"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the May girl?",
      "answer": ["kim lip", "kimlip"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the June girl?",
      "answer": ["jinsoul"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the July girl?",
      "answer": ["choerry", "yerim"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the second November girl?",
      "answer": ["yves"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the second December girl?",
      "answer": ["chuu"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the second January girl?",
      "answer": ["go won", "gowon"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the March girl?",
      "answer": ["olivia hye", "hyejoo"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 1/3's concept?",
      "answer": ["innocent"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is ODD EYE CIRCLE's concept?",
      "answer": ["girl crush", "girlcrush"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is yyxy's concept?",
      "answer": ["youth"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What was LOONA's first Korean digital single?",
      "answer": ["the carol 2.0"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What was LOONA's first English digital single?",
      "answer": [
        "loonatic english version",
        "loonatic eng ver",
        "loonatic english ver"
      ],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which year did LOONA do a CF for Skoolooks?",
      "answer": ["2019"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which year did HeeJin and HyunJin do a CF for Avajar?",
      "answer": ["2018"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Which year did Heejin, HyunJin, YeoJin, ViVi, and Kim Lip do a CF for Law of Creation?",
      "answer": ["2017"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the name of BlockBerry Creative's pre-debut trainee searching project?",
      "answer": ["loonation"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "True or False: The amount of potential songs per album exceeded 1,000.",
      "answer": ["true"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of BlockBerry Creative's parent company?",
      "answer": ["polaris entertainment", "polaris"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "When did LOONA receive their first win?",
      "answer": ["march 12 2020", "march 12, 2020", "200412"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was Girl Front filmed??",
      "answer": ["los angeles", "la"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    },
    {
      "question": "What did HaSeul give to HyunJin in LOONA Kick #44?",
      "answer": ["chair", "a chair"],
      "reward": { "min": 5, "max": 10 }
    }
  ]
}
